A Guide to the James J. Kilpatrick Papers 1969-1978
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
James J. Kilpatrick Papers 1969-1978
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
6626-h
3500 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
The Library acquired these papers from James J. Kilpatrick on 26 Oct 1978.
Scope and Content Information
This collection contains files of Kilpatrick's personal correspondence, reader mail in response to his columns and television appearances, correspondence concerning his speeches, together with some notes for, and copies of, his talks, radio and television transcripts, magazine essays, and correspondence, proofs, and reviews for The Foxes Union(1977). Topics include abortion, federal arts subsidies, amnesty for draft evaders, the federal bureaucracy, the business community, President Jimmy Carter, censorship, school discipline, government aid to private schools, E.R.A., foreign affairs, particularly Rhodesia., inhospitable hotels, laetrile, Bert Lance, Medicare abuse and government regulation of hospitals and practitioners, Richard Nixon, the Panama Canal, U.S. politics, school busing, reverse discrimination, the Book of Common Prayer, abuse of freedom of the press, social security, tax cuts, and the teaching of English. The collection also includes a number of prominent correspondents writing brief notes on letters, generally in response to a column.
Contents List
- Personal Correspondence
  - Abzug-Avins, incl. w/ Spiro Agnew, Jack Anderson 1974-1976 (Box 1)
  - Bachman-Biossat, incl. w/Birch Bayh, Howard H. Baker, Jr. 1974-1976 (Box 1)
  - Black-Bryant 1971-1976 (Box 1)
  - Buben-Byrd, incl. w/ Chief Justice Warren Earl Burger, Earl L. Butz, Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1974-1976 (Box 1)
  - Burford, Lolah 1969-1977 (Box 1)
  - Callaway-Clore, incl. w/Frank Church 1971-1976 (Box 1)
  - Coca-Cola-Corbett 1972-1976 (Box 1)
  - Costello-Currin 1971-1976 (Box 2)
  - Dabney-Drew 1973-1977 (Box 2)
  - Du Beau-Dwyer 1973-1976 (Box 2)
  - Early-Evans, incl. w/Sam J. Ervin, Jr. 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - Fall-Flittie 1973-1976 (Box 2)
  - Floran-Fugate, incl. w/Jerry Ford 1973-1977 (Box 2)
  - Fund for Investigative Journalism Aug 1969-Oct 1974 (Box 2)
  - Galbraith-Geoghegan, incl. w/John Kenneth Galbraith 1972-1976 (Box 2)
  - Giles-Gureghian, incl. w/Mills Godwin, Barry Goldwater 1972-1976 (Box 3)
  - Hagan-Healy 1973-1976 (Box 3)
  - Heartwell-Hoover, incl. w/Linwood Holton, J. Edgar Hoover 1971-1976 (Box 3)
  - Howard, A.E. Dick--Woodrow Wilson Fellowship Feb 1972-Nov 1975 (Box 3)
  - Hopkins-Hyatt, incl. w/Hubert Humphrey, Howard Hunt 1974-1976 (Box 3)
  - Ibach-Ivie 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - Jackson-Johnson, incl. w/Henry M. (Scoop) Jackson, Leon Jaworski 1971-1976 (Box 3)
  - Jones-Judges 1974-1976 (Box 3)
  - Kaeuper-Kuhn, incl. w/Marvin Kalb, Clarence Kelley, Edward M. Kennedy 1974-1977 (Box 3)
  - Lake-Lucus 1974-1976 (Box 4)
  - McCaffrey-McNelly incl. w/Eugene McCarthy 1972-1976 (Box 4)
  - Macmillan-Milstein 1973-1977 (Box 4)
  - Mintz-Muskie, incl. w/Walter F. Mondale, Edmund S. Muskie 1972-1976 (Box 4)
  - Namey-Novak 1973-1976 (Box 4)
  - O'Brien-Ortona 1973-1976 (Box 4)
  - Packwood-Pulliam, incl. w/William Proxmire 1970-1977 (Box 4)
  - Rappahannock-Richardson, incl. w/Eliot Richardson 1972-1976 (Box 4)
  - Rickenbacker-Ryan 1973-1976 (Box 4)
  - Seaman-Wertaur 1975-1976 (Box 4)
- Reader Mail Jan-Jun 1977
  - Abortion Jun 1977 (Box 5)
  - "Agronsky & Co." Dec 1976-Jan 1977 (Box 5)
  - Aliens Apr 1977 (Box 5)
  - Amnesty Jan-Feb 1977 (Box 5)
  - Armed Forces Mar-Jun 1977 (Box 5)
  - Assassinations Mar-Apr 1977 (Box 5)
  - Bilderbergers Mar 1977 (Box 5)
  - Books Jan-Mar 1977 (Box 5)
  - Bureaucracy Nov 1976-Jun 1977, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Business Jan 1976-Jun 1977 (Box 5)
  - Carter, Jimmy Jan-Jun 1977, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Censorship Mar-Apr 1977 (Box 5)
  - Central Intelligence Agency Jan-Jun 1977 (Box 5)
  - Communism Jan-Jun 1977 (Box 5)
  - Congress Jan-May 1977 (Box 5)
  - Conservation Jan-Jun 1977 (Box 5)
  - Conservatism Jan-May 1977 (Box 5)
  - Constitution Jan-Sep 1977 (Box 6)
  - Consumerism Feb-Jun 1977 (Box 6)
  - Crime Jan-Jun 1977 (Box 6)
  - Dirigibles Jan-Feb 1977 (Box 6)
  - Economy Jan-Jun 1977 (Box 6)
  - Education Jan-Jul 1977 (Box 6)
  - Elections Apr 1977 (Box 6)
  - Electoral Reform Mar-Jun 1977 (Box 6)
  - Energy Jan-Jun (Box 6)
  - Environment Jan-Jun 1977 (Box 6)
  - Equal Rights Amendment Feb-Jun 1977, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Fairlie, Henry Jan 1977 (Box 6)
  - Family Feb-Mar 1977 (Box 6)
  - Fan Mail Jan-May 1977 (Box 6)
  - Foreign Affairs Jan-Jun 1977 (Box 6)
  - Funeral Jan 1977 (Box 6)
  - Handicapped May-Jun 1977 (Box 6)
  - Health Care Dec 1976-Jun 1977, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Homosexuals Jun 1977 (Box 7)
  - Inflation Jan 1977 (Box 7)
  - Journalism Mar 1977 (Box 7)
  - Labor Jan-Jun 1977 (Box 7)
  - Law Feb-Jun 1977 (Box 7)
  - McCarthy, Eugene Jan 1977 (Box 7)
  - Military Dec 1976-Apr 1977 (Box 7)
  - Nation's Business Jan-Feb 1977 (Box 7)
  - Newspaper Writing Jan-Jul 1977 (Box 7)
  - Nixon, Richard Feb-Jun 1977 (Box 7)
  - Nut Mail Jan-Mar 1977 (Box 7)
  - Obscenity Mar 1977 (Box 7)
  - Occupational Safety and Health Administration Dec 1976-Apr 1977 (Box 7)
  - Panama Canal Jan-Jun 1977 (Box 7)
  - Pensions Jan 1977 (Box 7)
  - Poetry May 1977 (Box 7)
  - Politics Jan-Jul 1977 (Box 7)
  - Pornography Mar-Jun 1977 (Box 7)
  - Postal Service Jan-Jun 1977 (Box 8)
  - Press Jan-Jun 1977 (Box 8)
  - Promotion Jan-Apr 1977 (Box 8)
  - Race Dec 1976-Jun 1977, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Reagan, Ronald Feb 1977 (Box 8)
  - Regrets Jan-Jul 1977 (Box 8)
  - Religion Jan-May 1976, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Rhodesia Mar-Jun 1977 (Box 8)
  - Satire Jan-May 1977 (Box 8)
  - "Sixty Minutes" Feb-Jul 1977 (Box 8)
  - Social Security Jan-Jun 1977 (Box 8)
  - Sport Jan 1977 (Box 8)
  - Supreme Court Feb-Jun 1977 (Box 8)
  - Taxation Jan-May 1977 (Box 8)
  - TV Scotus Jan 1977 (Box 8)
  - Television Apr-May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Terrorists Mar 1977 (Box 8)
  - Thank Yous Dec 1976-Apr 1977 (Box 8)
  - Transportation Jan-Jun 1977 (Box 8)
  - United Nations Jun 1977 (Box 8)
  - Veterans Dec 1976 (Box 8)
  - Voting Rights Mar-May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Washington Star Syndicate May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Washington Star Syndicate: Permissions Jan-Jun 1977 (Box 8)
  - Washington Star Syndicate: Promotion Jan-Mar 1977 (Box 8)
  - Welfare May-Jun 1977 (Box 8)
  - Writing Jan-Jun 1977 (Box 8)
- Reader Mail Jul-Dec 1977
  - Abortion Jul-Dec 1977 (Box 9)
  - Agriculture Oct-Dec 1977 (Box 9)
  - "Agronsky & Co." Aug 1977 (Box 9)
  - Airbags Jul-Oct 1977 (Box 9)
  - Aliens Jul-Sep 1977 (Box 9)
  - Armed Services Jul-Aug 1977 (Box 9)
  - Arts Sep-Oct 1977 (Box 9)
  - Barges Jul-Aug 1977 (Box 9)
  - Books Oct-Dec 1977 (Box 9)
  - Bureaucracy Jul-Sep 1977, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Business Jul-Nov 1977 (Box 9)
  - Callaway, Howard (Bo) Jul 1977 (Box 9)
  - Carter, Jimmy Jun-Dec 1977 (Box 9)
  - Central Intelligence Agency Nov 1977 (Box 9)
  - Cigarettes Dec 1977 (Box 9)
  - Civil Service Oct 1977 (Box 9)
  - Communism Jul-Nov 1977 (Box 9)
  - Congress Sep-Oct 1977 (Box 9)
  - Conservation Aug-Dec 1977 (Box 9)
  - Conservatism Aug 1977-Jan 1978 (Box 9)
  - Constitution Jul 1977-Jan 1978 (Box 9)
  - Consumerism Aug-Dec 1977 (Box 9)
  - Crime Jul-Oct 1977 (Box 9)
  - Dirigibles Oct 1977 (Box 9)
  - Drugs Sep 1977 (Box 9)
  - Economy Aug-Oct 1977 (Box 9)
  - Education Jul 1977, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Elections Nov-Dec 1977 (Box 10)
  - Electoral Reform Aug-Oct 1977 (Box 10)
  - Energy Aug-Dec 1977 (Box 10)
  - Environment Jul-Dec 1977 (Box 10)
  - Equal Rights Amendment Jul 1977-Jan 1978, 4 folders (Box 10)
  - Ethics Sep 1977 (Box 10)
  - Family Dec 1977 (Box 10)
  - Fan Mail Jul 1977-Jan 1978 (Box 11)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation Nov 1977 (Box 11)
  - Federal Communications Commission Aug 1977 (Box 11)
  - Firearms Sep 1977 (Box 11)
  - Foreign Affairs Jul-Dec 1977 (Box 11)
  - Genetics Dec 1977 (Box 11)
  - Handicapped Jul-Oct 1977 (Box 11)
  - Health Care May-Dec 1977 (Box 11)
  - Homosexuals Jul 1977 (Box 11)
  - Hotels Oct 1977-Jan 1978 (Box 11)
  - Industry Sep-Oct 1977 (Box 11)
  - Inflation Nov 1977 (Box 11)
  - Labor Sep-Oct 1977 (Box 11)
  - Laetrile Jul 1977-Jan 1978 (Box 11)
  - Lance, Bert Sep-Dec 1977 (Box 11)
  - Law Sep-Dec 1977 (Box 11)
  - Maritime Oct 1977 (Box 11)
  - Military Oct 1977 (Box 11)
  - Newspaper Writing Aug-Dec 1977 (Box 11)
  - Nixon, Richard Jul-Sep 1977 (Box 11)
  - Nut Mail Dec 1977 (Box 11)
  - Panama Canal Aug-Dec 1977 (Box 12)
  - Politics Apr-Dec 1977 (Box 12)
  - Population Oct 1977 (Box 12)
  - Pornography Sep 1977 (Box 12)
  - Postal Service Jul-Nov 1977 (Box 12)
  - Press Sep-Oct 1977 (Box 12)
  - Privacy Aug 1977 (Box 12)
  - Race Jul-Dec 1977, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Reading Jul-Aug 1977 (Box 12)
  - Reagan, Ronald Dec 1977 (Box 12)
  - Real Estate Oct 1977 (Box 12)
  - Regrets Jun 1977-Jan 1978 (Box 12)
  - Religion Aug-Sep 1977 (Box 12)
  - Retirement Oct 1977 (Box 12)
  - Rhodesia Jul-Aug 1977 (Box 12)
  - Satire Sep 1977 (Box 12)
  - Science Aug-Sep 1977 (Box 12)
  - Scientology Aug-Oct 1977 (Box 12)
  - Scrabble Jul-Aug 1977 (Box 12)
  - Scrabble Sep-Dec 1977 (Box 13)
  - "Sixty Minutes" Aug 1977-Jan 1978 (Box 13)
  - Social Security Jul 1977-Jan 1978, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Sodium Valporate Aug-Oct 1977 (Box 13)
  - Subscriptions Feb-Jul 1977 (Box 13)
  - Supreme Court Jul-Nov 1977 (Box 13)
  - Taiwan Aug 1977 (Box 13)
  - Taxation Oct-Dec 1977 (Box 13)
  - Television Aug-Dec 1977 (Box 13)
  - Thank Yous Jan 1978 (Box 13)
  - Transportation Jul 1977-Jan 1978 (Box 13)
  - United Nations Nov 1977 (Box 13)
  - Veterans Oct 1977 (Box 13)
  - Voting Rights Dec 1977 (Box 13)
  - Washington Star Syndicate Nov-Dec 1977 (Box 13)
  - Washington Star Syndicate: Permissions Jul-Dec 1977 (Box 13)
  - Washington Star Syndicate: Promotions n.d. (Box 13)
  - Welfare Jul-Dec 1977 (Box 13)
  - Writing Jul 1977-Jan 1978, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Youth Camps Jul 1977 (Box 13)
- Speech Files
  - Speech Notes: Medical Jun 1969 (Box 13)
  - Speech Notes: "The Presidency" 1972 (Box 13)
  - Speech Notes: Miscellaneous Jan 1974-Oct 1975, n.d. (Box 13)
  - Speech Notes: Bicentennial Nov 1975, Jan 1976 (Box 13)
  - Speech Notes: The Presidency 1972 Sep 1976 (Box 14)
  - Speech Notes: "Dissenting Opinion" n.d. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Press Association 10 Jan 1976 (Box 14)
  - American Bakers Association 15 Jan 1976 (Box 14)
  - Macon Junior College 16 Jan 1976 (Box 14)
  - Christ Church School 20 Jan 1976 (Box 14)
  - Alfalfa Dinner 24 Jan 1976 (Box 14)
  - Saginaw Valley College 27 Jan 1976 (Box 14)
  - National Town Meeting 28 Jan 1976 (Box 14)
  - Embassy of Israel 30 Jan 1976 (Box 14)
  - University of Tennessee 5 Feb 1976 (Box 14)
  - Sigma Delta Chi 6 Feb 1976 (Box 14)
  - Student Bar Association 10 Feb 1976 (Box 14)
  - Allegheny Ludlum Industries 13 Feb 1976 (Box 14)
  - Georgia Press Association 20 Feb 1976 (Box 14)
  - Tuckahoe Woman's Club 25 Feb 1976 (Box 14)
  - Bank Management Association, Lexington, Kentucky 3 Mar 1976 (Box 14)
  - Southern Methodist University 10 Mar 1976 (Box 14)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Grand Island, Nebraska 11 Mar 1976 (Box 14)
  - Horizons, Winston-Salem, North Carolina 16 Mar 1976 (Box 14)
  - Lafayette College, Easton, Pennsylvania 29 Mar 1976 (Box 14)
  - The Proprietary Association 5 Apr 1976 (Box 14)
  - University of Arkansas 6 Apr 1976 (Box 14)
  - American Society for Information Services 13 Apr 1976 (Box 14)
  - University of South Carolina 14 Apr 1976 (Box 14)
  - Georgia Southern College 21 Apr 1976 (Box 14)
  - Young Americans for Freedom Field Day 24 Apr 1976 (Box 14)
  - University of Virginia Club of Washington 27 Apr 1976 (Box 14)
  - Heritage Club, La Crosse, Wisconsin 29 Apr 1976 (Box 14)
  - White House Correspondents Association 1 May 1976 (Box 14)
  - Houston Personnel Association 18 May 1976 (Box 14)
  - Hillcrest Children's Center Benefit 20 May 1976 (Box 14)
  - Stanford University 25 May 1976 (Box 14)
  - College of Marin 26 May 1976 (Box 14)
  - Washington Journalism Center 2 Jun 1976 (Box 14)
  - Rappahannock High School 4 Jun 1976 (Box 14)
  - Security Trust Co. 7 Jun 1976 (Box 14)
  - Edison Electric Institute 9 Jun 1976 (Box 14)
  - Society of Professional Journalists 11 Jun 1976 (Box 14)
  - Northern Virginia Chamber of Commerce 15 Jun 1976 (Box 14)
  - National Education Association 26 Jun 1976 (Box 14)
  - Federal Intercredit Bank 9 Jul 1976 (Box 14)
  - International Platform Association 29 Jul 1976 (Box 14)
  - Southern Governor's Conference 1 Sep 1976 (Box 14)
  - Conservative Activists 10 Sep 1976 (Box 14)
  - University of Texas 14 Sep 1976 (Box 15)
  - East Carolina University 21 Sep 1976 (Box 15)
  - National Agricultural Chemicals Association 28 Sep 1976 (Box 15)
  - Public Relations Society of America 5 Oct 1976 (Box 15)
  - Jefferson Award 5 Oct 1976 (Box 15)
  - National Products Association 8 Oct 1976 (Box 15)
  - Spartanburg Methodist College 12 Oct 1976 (Box 15)
  - Atlanta Bar Association 15 Oct 1976 (Box 15)
  - Paperboard Packaging 19 Oct 1976 (Box 15)
  - Audit Bureau of Circulations, University of Wisconsin, Whitewater 20 Oct 1976 (Box 15)
  - Manufacturing Chemists Association 5 Nov 1976 (Box 15)
  - National Wholesale Druggists 10 Nov 1976 (Box 15)
  - Denver Executives Club 11 Nov 1976 (Box 15)
  - Sigma Delta Chi 11 Nov 1976 (Box 15)
  - Louisiana Teachers Association 23 Nov 1976 (Box 15)
  - Roth Enterprises 9 Dec 1976 (Box 15)
  - Minnesota House of Representatives 11 Dec 1976 (Box 15)
  - VPI TV Material 15 Dec 1976 (Box 15)
  - Williamsburg Trip 25 Dec 1976 (Box 15)
  - National Independent Meatpackers Association 26 Jan 1977 (Box 15)
  - Jacobi Medical Society 5 Feb 1977 (Box 15)
  - National Ocean Industries Association 14 Mar 1977 (Box 15)
  - Federal Land Bank of Baltimore 15 Mar 1977 (Box 15)
  - Tax Executive Institute 16 Mar 1977 (Box 15)
  - Army Mutual Aid Association 18 Mar 1977 (Box 15)
  - Norfolk Forum 22 Mar 1977 (Box 15)
  - International Order of the Golden Rule 22 Mar 1977 (Box 15)
  - AETNA 24 Mar 1977 (Box 15)
  - Harding College 4 Apr 1977 (Box 15)
  - University of Kentucky 6 Apr 1977 (Box 15)
  - High School Speech, Culpeper 12 Apr 1977 (Box 15)
  - Mercer University 20 Apr 1977 (Box 15)
  - Fuel Merchants of New Jersey 21 Apr 1977 (Box 15)
  - Michigan Funeral Directors Association 4 May 1977 (Box 15)
  - Troy State University 5 May 1977 (Box 15)
  - Nixon/Frost Mutual Broadcasting 12 May 1977 (Box 15)
  - Texas Hospital Association 24 May 1977 (Box 15)
  - National Consumer Finance 25 May 1977 (Box 15)
  - New York State Funeral Directors Association 14 Jun 1977 (Box 15)
  - American Health Care Association 16 Jun 1977 (Box 15)
  - National Retail Hardware Store 21 Jul 1977 (Box 15)
  - Government Communications Lunch 27 Jul 1977 (Box 16)
  - Kennedy Center Meeting 3 Aug 1977 (Box 16)
  - American Bar Association 7 Aug 1977 (Box 16)
  - Davenport College, Grand Rapids, Michigan 13 Sep 1977 (Box 16)
  - Richmond Metropolitan Hospital 14 Sep 1977 (Box 16)
  - Associated Risk Managers International 19 Sep 1977 (Box 16)
  - American University 22 Sep 1977 (Box 16)
  - President's Commission on Personal Interchange 23 Sep 1977 (Box 16)
  - National Electrical Contractors Association 26 Sep 1977 (Box 16)
  - International Reading Association 29 Sep 1977 (Box 16)
  - National Selected Morticians, Atlanta, Goergia 4 Oct 1977 (Box 16)
  - Western Carolina University 5 Oct 1977 (Box 16)
  - Private Practice 12 Oct 1977 (Box 16)
  - Petersburg Public Forum 13 Oct 1977 (Box 16)
  - Associated Press Managing Editors Association 26 Oct 1977 (Box 16)
  - High Point Executives Club, High Point, North Carolina 1 Nov 1977 (Box 16)
  - Jack Morton Productions for Brick Association 7 Nov 1977 (Box 16)
  - Mortgage Bankers Association 7 Nov 1977 (Box 16)
  - Southern Medical Association 8 Nov 1977 (Box 16)
  - Florida Council of 100, Palm Beach 10 Nov 1977 (Box 16)
  - York Commemorative Conference, York, Pennsylvania 14 Nov 1977 (Box 16)
  - National School Supply & Equipment Association 15 Nov 1977 (Box 16)
  - OMNI Meeting 16 Nov 1977 (Box 16)
  - National Press Club 17 Nov 1977 (Box 16)
  - Connecticut Business & Industry Association 22 Nov 1977 (Box 16)
  - Luncheon, White Walnut Hill 4 Dec 1977 (Box 16)
  - National League of Cities, San Francisco 6 Dec 1977 (Box 16)
  - White House Fellows 16 Dec 1977 (Box 16)
  - Gerald Ford Dinner 20 Dec 1977 (Box 16)
- Radio and TV Transcripts
  - WTOP Commentaries 1976 (Box 16)
  - WGBH TV: "Advocates on Amnesty" Feb 1973 (Box 17)
  - TV Transcripts 1974 (Box 17)
  - Chamber of Commerce Script: "Speak Up" [13 Feb 1975] (Box 17)
  - Canadian Broadcasting System 30 Jul 1976 (Box 17)
  - WPIX-TV: "Dinah Shore Show" 31 Oct 1977 (Box 17)
- Magazine Articles and Related Material
  - Nation's Business: "The Nation's Business Washington Letter" Jun 1978 (Box 17)
  - National Review: "State of the Union" 1 Mar 1974 (Box 17)
  - National Review: "The Portuguese Atrocity that didn't Happen" Apr-May 1974 (Box 17)
  - National Review: "The Goldwater and Reagan Campaigns: A Difference?" Dec 1975 (Box 17)
  - National Review: "A Few Reflections on Kansas City" Aug-Sep 1976 (Box 17)
  - Prism: "Something's Happened to Tom!" Aug-Nov 1975 (Box 17)
  - Saturday Review: Jimmy Carter Nov-Dec 1976 (Box 17)
  - TV Guide: "TV Opinion Has a Place--As TV Opinion" Jul 1974-May 1975 (Box 17)
  - U.S. Steel News: "The Bicentennial Bequest" Dec 1975-Feb 1976 (Box 17)
- Material re The Foxes' Union
  - The Foxes' Union: General Correspondence Jul 1970-Apr 1977 (Box 17)
  - The Foxes' Union: Promotion Apr 1977-Sep 1978, n.d. (Box 17)
  - The Foxes' Union: Page Proofs 1977 (Box 17)
  - The Foxes' Union: Book Reviews Sep 1977-Aug 1978, 2 folders (Box 17)
- Miscellaneous
  - Appointment Calendar 1976 (Box 17)
  - Photographs of Kilpatrick and White Walnut Hill Farm, Scrabble, Virginia n.d. (Box 17)